[theme music]
Okay, girls, we have
to name our new puppy.
Michelle, do you have
a name for the puppy?
Yes. Michelle.
That's your name.
I like my name.
Mr. Bear and I have
the perfect name. Mr. Dog.
Mr. Dog?
Steph, when you
have a kid someday
what are you gonna
name it, Mr. Baby?
Not if it's a girl.
I think we should
name the puppy
something that fits
its personality.
Like Puddles.
Dad, I have
the perfect name. Comet.
Because he's fast
and he's got a tail.
And he only hits the newspaper
once every 76 years.
Comet. I can live with that.
I like Michelle.
[instrumental music]
[Jesse Frederick singing
"Everywhere You Look"]
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ What ever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milk man
the paper boy evenin' TV ♪
♪ Ahh ahh ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold onto ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a place ♪
♪ Of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waiting
to carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-dow ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Oh, what is taking
your dad so long?
Danny, come on! We're gonna
miss our plane to LA.
I'm comin', I'm comin'.
Guys, don't forget
to watch our show tomorrow.
Not only are we live
from "Fashion Expo '90"
but Danny and I are gonna get
total fashion makeovers.
That's right,
I'm leaving as Danny Tanner
but I'll be returning
as Danny Style.
Dad, when you're gone, can
Comet sleep with me in my bed?
No, honey, Comet
sleeps in the kitchen
and I don't want to hear
about you sleeping in his box.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Bye, Dad. Have fun.
- Bye.
- You too.
- See you, guys.
- Goodbye.
- See you later.
- Have fun, guys.
- 'Fly safe.'
- Okay.
Okay, now it's time
for my extra sloppy
can't help but make a mess
but it's okay
'cause Danny's out of town
ice cream sundaes!
Comet wants a sundae too.
Steph, Comet's a dog,
if he wants a sundae
tell him to go chase
the Good Humor man.
Okay, Michelle, here you go.
And Deej, knock yourself out.
Thank you.
Michelle, look! Pee-wee Herman!
Where's Pee-wee Herman?
(Joey)
'Hey, Steph.
What are you doin'?'
Hey, a doggy ate my ice cream.
Alright, alright.
Here, here, here.
I'll take the dog. Come on.
Bad doggy.
Michelle, don't have a cow.
- Bad doggy.
- Here, trade with D.J.
I don't want a dish
of doggy drool.
[doorbell dings]
I'll get it.
Uncle Jesse?
Yes, may I help you?
Doggy ate my ice cream.
The doggy ate your ows cream?
Ah, come here,
I'll cheer you up.
Come on, let's
cheer Michelle up, shall we?
- 'Okay.'
- Okay, you wanna sing?
[clears throat]
Alright, where is he?
Alright, where is who?
The Jessman. The Big J.
The Jester himself.
Where is he, man? I haven't seen
him in three years.
He's in the kitchen
with the girls.
Girls? Yeah? Alright,
it's the same old Jess.
[laughs]
I mean, it's like
he knew I was coming here.
♪ The farmer in the dell
the farmer in the dell ♪
♪ Heigh ho the derry-o
♪ The cheese sleeps alone
the cheese sleeps alone ♪
Yo. Mother goose.
- Pete Bianco, you dirtbag!
- You filth ball.
- You scum bucket.
- You lowlife.
- Give me a hug!
- Ha ha ha, how you doing?
- Good! How you doing?
- Great, man.
Hey, you were supposed
to call me
when you got back from Europe.
That's what I'm doing, I just
got back, man, oh,
what a-what a trip.
I learned how to say trust me,
babe, in 12 different languages.
- Well, you look great, man.
- You too, man.
That's a-that's a
very festive apron
we're wearing today,
ain't it?
The guy is always on my case.
Remember the first time
we met, that first
we got in this huge fight
over these two girls.
Oh, why, that's right,
uh, uh, the Scarcella twins.
That's right, that's right.
Donna and Barbara, remember?
That's right, we're beating
each other's heads up
against the locker
we finally stop and realize,
this is stupid.
(together)
There's two of 'em.
[both laughing]
Anyway, Pete Bianco,
this is, uh, my niece D.J.
- Hi.
- D.J.
Stephanie and Michelle.
Hello.
The doggy ate my ice cream.
And this is my pal
and my partner
in the advertising business,
Joseph Gladstone.
Hey, Pete and I go all the way
back to the livin' room.
I just heard something.
You-you're in advertising
now, Jess?
What? Are you turning
into a suit on me? Huh?
What happened
to the old Dr. Dare
I used to know and love?
Who's Dr. Dare?
This guy right here.
Your uncle was a wild man.
This guy never turned down
a dare. Am I right?
- That's right.
- You're looking soft there.
- Get out.
- Still think that, oh, yeah.
Well, well, still think
you can keep up with me?
- Please! It's a piece of cake.
- Huh?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I dare you, I dare you to
keep up with me for two days.
- You got it, chief.
- Yeah?
Let's jump on our bikes
and tear this town apart.
I'll show you what
a Dr. Dare is about.
- You got it. You got it.
- Whoa!
Dr. Dare rides again!
But not in this apron.
[instrumental music]
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ I said Louie Louie ♪
♪ Oh baby I said we gotta go ♪
Shh! Kids are sleeping.
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Louie oh baby.. ♪
♪ I said Louie Louie ♪
♪ Oh baby I said we gotta go.. ♪
What's going on out there?
I don't know.
Let's go find out.
Comet, you stay there
and keep my pillow warm and dry.
Here we go.
♪ I I don't know the words ♪
♪ Nobody does so
let's go back to the chorus ♪
♪ I said Louie Louie
♪ Oh baby I said we gotta go ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah
I said Louie Louie ♪
♪ Oh baby I said we gotta go ♪
(Jesse)
'Chorus.'
♪ Louie Louie oh baby ♪
♪ I said we gotta go ♪
♪ Louie Louie oh baby
I said we gotta go ♪
Hey guys, come on,
you're gonna..
You're gonna wake up
the girls.
No, you got them all.
[Jesse laughs]
Joey, I'm glad
you're here. Listen.
I need a big favor, Pete and I
are driving up to
Lake Tahoe on our bikes.
I'm telling you this feels
like the old days, man.
What you gotta do is cover
for me. Thanks, Joey.
Yeah, thanks, Joey.
Oh, and, uh, don't worry
we'll be back here
in time for the party, okay?
Oh, wait a second, uh.
- What party?
- What?
It's a big reunion. We got
the whole band back together.
That's right, and you guys
are all invited because
uh, well, because
you live here, bye.
Alright! Party!
You two, back to bed. Let's go.
- Ow!
- So mean.
(D.J.)
'But tomorrow night,
party, party!'
Okay, Michelle.
Let's get you into..
Well, who is this?
Bad doggy.
Michelle, why
are you mad at Comet?
The doggy ate
my ice cream.
Remember?
Well, come here, Comet.
Yeah?
[gibberish]
Comet says, "he's very sorry."
And, uh, look,
his tail's waggin'.
That means he loves
you very, very much.
Okay, we're friends.
[indistinct chatter]
Alright, tell them about that
story about New Year's eve.
- Where was it?
- Baja.
Baja. Tell them about
that story. Tell them.
Oh, oh, yeah,
oh, yeah, We-we-we, uh
we took over
this little cantina..
and we-and we did a Mariachi
version of "Love Stinks," right?
That's right. And it stunk.
Oh, wait, but after
after we met
those little Senoritas and..
So then, what happened?
Well, so then, we-we-we took
the nice Senoritas to a museum
and we taught them all about
the history of El Pollo Loco.
Yeah, we, uh, we had
some wild times.
- That's right.
- We have wild times too.
Last month,
Uncle Jesse organized
my class trip to the dairy.
Whoa, life in the fast lane, eh?
Hi, I'm Joey Gladstone.
I'm Jesse's partner.
Hi, I'm Donna,
Jesse's old girlfriend.
He looks great tonight,
doesn't he?
Yeah, I was just thinkin'
the same thing myself.
Hi, Pete.
Hi, Michelle.
Isn't it past your bedtime?
I don't know.
I can't tell time.
[drumming]
- All set, guys. Let's do it.
- 'Alright.'
Hey, alright now,
listen up, everybody.
I know that we said we'd, uh,
we'd never play together again.
But I figure if
The Who and The Stones
can get back together,
so can Feedback.
That's right. So let's hit it.
[guitar music]
Feedback lives! Ow!
[instrumental music]
♪ You know you make me wanna ♪
♪ Shout ♪
♪ Kick my heels up and ♪
♪ Throw my hands up and ♪
♪ Shout ♪
♪ Throw my head back and ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Shout ♪
♪ Don't forget to say you will ♪
♪ Don't forget to say hey ♪
♪ Shout ♪
♪ I still remember ♪
♪ Doo wop ♪
♪ When you used to be
nine years old ♪
♪ Shooby doo wop do
wop wop wop ♪
♪ When I was a fool for you
from the bottom of my soul ♪
♪ You make me wanna ♪
♪ Shout ♪
♪ Kick my heels up and ♪
♪ Throw my hands up and ♪
♪ Shout ♪
♪ Throw my head back and ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Don't forget to say you will ♪
♪ Don't forget to say hey oh ♪
♪ A little bit softer now ♪
Alligator!
[cheering]
D.J., did you ever see
anyone do this before?
Once. When a bee flew
into Dad's shorts.
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Shout shout shout ♪
♪ Jump Jump Jump ♪
♪ Jump jump jump ♪
♪ Jump jump jump ♪♪
Party, dude!
♪ Well I got a woman
mean as she can be ♪
♪ I got a woman
♪ Well some a times I think
she's almost as mean as me ♪
♪ I said I got a woman
mean as she can be ♪♪
Oh and boy, does she look mean.
[instrumental music]
Everybody, I-I'd like
you to meet
the love of my life,
Rebecca Donaldson.
And quite frankly, doesn't she
look beautiful this evening?
Who's the blonde?
Well, this is my
old girlfriend, Donna.
My old, old, old girlfriend.
- Hi, Becky.
- Hello, Donna.
Why don't we go meet some people
I haven't dated, shall we?
Danny, is that really you?
Yes, Joey, and I would
be really steamed
if I did not look so cool.
Well, may I say that you look
just like cappuccino come alive.
Oh, thank you, Joey, Joey, Joey.
But look around at these people.
They have no sense of style.
- Jesse, can I talk to you?
- Excuse me.
Look, I have everything
under control.
You look very cute, by the way.
Girls, it's time to go to bed.
(all)
Aw!
Jess, I'll say goodnight
to the girls
and you say goodnight to Donna.
[chuckles]
- Okay, Michelle. Time for bed.
- No more party?
No more party.
Ah, nuts.
Well, girls, what do you think
of your new rad, bad dad?
Daddy, you look so handsome
I want to take you
to show-and-tell.
Ah, thank you, Stephanie.
That dog slept in your room
last night, didn't he?
"Twist and Shout."
What do you say, Tony? Let's go.
(male #1)
'Kick it.'
Who-o-o-a, fellas.
Come on, come on.
Cool it. Cool it now.
The little munchkins have
to go nighty-night.
(male #2)
'Seriously?'
Uh, kids-kids
are going beddy-bye.
Beddy-bye.
Well, you definitely
have changed, Jess.
You've gone from, uh
from Dr. Dare to Dr. Seuss.
What? I'm.. Uh, you don't think
I'm the same guy?
- Oh, Rog, give me that tape.
- What tape?
Everybody everybody have a seat
on the couch over here.
I got a surprise for you.
This is my life or something?
What are we doing?
Alright, this
is for you, my man.
Alright, now, the year,
the year is 1983.
The song on the jukebox
is "Maniac."
And the man on the motorcycle
is the one, the only..
...Dr. Dare.
[cheering]
We're here on the roof
of the State Street garage
where Dr. Dare has been
dared to do the impossible.
To ride his motorcycle on the
ledge of a six-story building.
- 'Yeah!'
- 'Yes.'
The doctor is about to operate.
Aren't you a little
over dramatic there?
Not if you die.
Hey, look, I was dared,
so I'm gonna do it.
Not without a kiss
for luck first.
- Have mercy.
- Now, don't waste tape on this.
This is disgusting.
'Please, don't waste tape.
Thank you.'
- 'Come on, Roger.'
- 'Alright.'
- Let's do it!
- 'Yeah!'
[cheering]
Look out!
- Alright.
- Here we go.
No, wait a minute,
wait there wait a minute.
Come here, Rog.
Come on. Don't go yet.
Alright, Rog, get a shot
of the drop.
(Jesse)
'Gettin' it, Rog?'
(Pete)
'Do yourself a favor,
Jess. Don't fall.'
Don't worry about it.
Alright, come here.
I wanna say one more thing.
Kids, don't try this at home.
Let's do it!
(Pete)
'Alright, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, we're not ready yet.'
'Hang on. Come here, Rog.'
[bike engine revving]
(Jesse)
'Have mercy!'
[cheering]
Thank you, thank you very much.
(Pete)
Hoo hoo! Alright.
Hey, wait a minute. Wait
a minute, wait a minute.
You guys think he was
tough back then?
You gotta see Dr. Suess now
carpooling second graders
to the dairy.
[laughing]
Come on, what,
you think I couldn't take
that ledge again if I wanted to?
What, are you kidding me?
No way...no way.
- Not a chance.
- Nope.
No way.
Follow me.
(male #3)
'Where's he going?'
[indistinct chatter]
Hey. Hey, Jesse.
Jesse! Hang on a second, man.
Jess, get back here.
This is stupid.
Joey, what's happening?
- Come on, we gotta go.
- Where?
- I'll tell you on the way.
- What, uh?
Come on.
[engine revving]
What?
Are you nuts?
Hey, look, man,
I-I was just kidding
back there about all that
Dr. Seuss stuff.
- Nobody dared you to do this.
- I dared me to do this.
Well, I'm daring
you not to do it.
Look, Jesse, I-I just came back
here to see my best friend
and hang out like
we used to in the old days.
But it's not like
the old days, man?
- Yes, but so what?
- Alright.
That's easy for you to say.
Pete, you're living
your life the exact
same way we said we would, man.
You got no responsibilities.
You jump on your bike
when you want to
you go wherever you want to.
- So come. Come on.
- Maybe I will.
- Come on.
- First I gotta do this, man.
Because I gotta prove to myself
that I'm the same guy.
Alright, look. You wanna do
something dangerous?
Kiss Donna in front of Becky.
Ah, come on, man, what's
the worst that could happen?
Don't answer that.
[car horn]
(Becky)
'Jesse!'
Jesse, just hold on
one second, young man.
Jesse Katsopolis.
I forbid you to do this.
Now, let's get
in the car and go home.
Becky, I know what I'm doin'.
Come on, you're being
an idiot. Get off the bike.
There's no way either
of you could understand this.
[bike engine revving]
Jesse! Would you get back here?
[dramatic music]
Jesse! Jesse,
please don't do this!
[music continues]
[engine revving]
Jess, oh, I'm
so happy you're alright.
Don't you ever scare
me like that again.
Now, get in that car
and get home right now, mister.
- Joey?
- Everyone else did it.
Go!
[instrumental music]
- Good seeing you, Jess.
- It's good seeing you, man.
- I gotta hit the road.
- I gotta hit the sack.
Gotta get up early tomorrow
and take Stephanie's class
to the fire station.
Living on the edge, aren't I?
Look. Ahem.
As far as tonight goes,
you didn't chicken out.
You just, uh, came
to your senses.
Oh, Dr. Sensible.
Doesn't quite have
the same ring, does it?
Hey, Jesse, maybe the guy
I came back here looking for
is not the same guy
anymore, but so what?
I like this guy too,
you know?
I'll tell you somethin' else.
You got a good thing
goin' here.
- I do, don't I?
- I love you, man.
Right back at you.
See you, dirt bucket.
See you, filth ball.
[bike engine revving]
Hi, Uncle Jesse.
Hey, Deej.
Joey told me
what happened tonight.
I'm glad you didn't
try that stunt.
D.J., I was this close.
I'm up on that ledge,
I'm this close to do it
and I chicken out.
Uncle Jesse..
..sometimes it takes
more courage to just say no.
Sounds pretty smart.
Where did you hear that from?
From you. And Nancy Reagan.
Well, Deej, I..
Maybe I'm smarter
than I was when I was 20
but let me tell you something
kid, I miss those old days.
I kind of remember you at 20.
You were this cool guy
with long hair
who'd drop by,
give me a present
and then ride away.
I like this Uncle Jesse
a lot better.
The one I see every day.
[instrumental music]
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'll tell you something.
When I was up there,
all I could do
was think about my family
and Becky and you girls.
I started thinking, you know,
if something happened to me
I'd miss out on
being part of your lives.
And there's nothing more
important to me than that.
Oh, maybe I gave up a little
bit, but I've also gained
quite a bit too, haven't I?
Yup. Goodnight, Dr. Dare.
Hey, that's
Uncle Dr. Dare to you.
Goodnight.
[guitar music]
I still got it.
♪ Ah ah ah ♪
[theme music]